- 我想  可以看出来了 -不错
- So, I guess that decides it. - Yup.
在咖啡屋待着
Hanging out at a coffee place
确实没有泡酒吧来得有趣
is not nearly as much fun as hanging out at a bar.
伙计  那是什么
Man, what's that?
哪个？
What?
那个卖咖啡的漂亮女孩 在你名字旁边画了颗心
That cute coffee girl wrote a heart by your name.
有人对你有意思
Somebody has a crush on you.
有人把你当成了我
Somebody thinks you're me.
你们真的认为她喜欢我?
Do you really think she likes me?
我是说  那也不用大惊小怪
I mean, I guess it's not that surprising.
每次我来这里 总能让她开怀大笑
Every time I come in here, I totally crack her up.
三周前
Marshall, here's your pumpkin latte.
马修  你的南瓜拿铁咖啡
你是怎么把南瓜放进 这么个小杯子?
Wow. How did you fit a pumpkin in this little cup?
-八天前 -给我来一杯南瓜拿铁咖啡
I'll have a pumpkin latte.
他们怎么能刚好把南瓜 放进这些小杯子？
How do they even fit a pumpkin in those little cups?
什么?  你们有个收缩激光吗
What? You got a shrink ray back there?
Yeah.
-昨天 -还记得吗？
Hey, remember that time I said that thing
那次我说的把南瓜放进杯子里的事?
about how do they fit a pumpkin into that little cup?
- 哪一次 - 第一次
- Which time? - The first time.
当然记得  很搞笑
Yeah. That was really funny.
是的
Right.
她觉得好笑只有两个原因
All right, there's only two reasons she'd laugh at that.
那是她这辈子听过的第一个笑话
One, it's the first joke she's ever heard,
或者 她喜欢你 你应该约她出来
or two, she likes you. You should totally ask her out.
你真这么想
You think?
你不和莉莉破镜重圆 不就是为了这个?
Yeah, that why you're not back with Lily, right?
这样才能体会到单身的乐趣
So you can experience what it's like to be single.
如果这颗心没有任何含意怎么办?
Well, what if the heart doesn't mean anything?
也许她在所有杯子上都画了呢
What if she writes it on all the cups?
我这杯就写了泰德  没有心
Mine says "Ted," no heart.
这杯写的...斯华利
Mine says... "Swarley."
他们怎么能把巴尼弄成了斯华利
How'd they get "Swarley" from "Barney"?
这都不算是名字
It's not even a name.
有谁会叫做斯华利?
Who would ever be called "Swarley"?
别叫我斯华利
Oh, please don't start calling me "Swarley."
酒吧里决不会发生这种事情
This would never happen at a bar!
老兄  斯华利怎么了
Man! What's up with Swarley?
你从没见过老斯华利那么烦燥吧
I know. You almost never see old Swarlz get that upset.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流
www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第二季 第七集
翻译：    沙萱     校对：     雨亦奇
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
知道吗?
Hey, guess what?
对不起
Oh, sorry.
是我妈妈
It's only my mom.
她只是像往常一样滔滔不绝
She's just rambling on like always.
怎么了
What happened?
马修有约会了
Marshall asked out a girl.
Wow.
是的  都是爸爸的错
Well, if anything, that's Dad's fault.
这样可以让她说上一阵子了
That'll keep her going a while.
当然是这样  你知道吗 有人帮了他一把
Oh, of course, you know, he had a little help.
斯华利  帮他?
Swarley hooked him up?
你抢了我的台词
Oh, good. You got my text.
- 是的 - 事实上是我帮了他一把
- Yeah. - Oh. No, it was me.
我传授给马修一个诀窍
I gave Marshall one of my secrets.
- 她怎么说 - 什么也没说
- So, what she say? - Nothing.
她肯定没听见我的话  她那么忙
I don't think she heard me. It's pretty busy up there.
什么?你摆对姿势了?
What? You gave her the look right?
低垂着头  眼睛向上
Head down, eyes looking up,
手插在口袋里  耸耸肩
hands in pockets, shoulders up,
再微微抬起头  含情脉脉  欲言又止
head slightly tilted, conveying shy vulnerability.
应该是吧
I think so.
我们还是走吧
Look, can we just go?
马修的南瓜拿铁咖啡
Pumpkin latte for Marshall.
我没点那个
I didn't order that.
电话号码
Phone number.
我喜欢那个形象
I love that look.
我跟你在一起 就是因为你害羞的样子
I think I slept with you because of that look.
难道那是装出来的?
And it's fake?
那你咬着嘴唇  羞涩转身
Oh, and you biting your lower lip, shyly looking away
再用力挺起胸 那不是装的?
and thrusting your chest out is natural?
你说对了
Yeah, I hear you.
- Hey! - Hey, guys.
明晚有空吗
Are you free tomorrow night?
我想开个品酒会
I was thinking of having a wine tasting slash
一个'公寓捕鼠记'的聚会
"help me catch the rat in my apartment" party.
真是好主意 你可以让人和鼠共享奶酪
That's a great idea. You can put out cheese for both.
我该邀请马修 对不对?
I  should invite Marshall, right?
如果我不请他会显得太小器
It'd be weird if I didn't.
是的  不过我想他去不了
Yeah, I don't think he can go.
是吗  为什么?
Really? Why not?
是这样
Uh, okay, um...
莉莉  有些事得跟你说
Lily, we have to tell you something.
马修已经佳人有约了
Marshall has a date.
恭喜他
Oh. Well... good for him.
当真?  你不介意?
Really? You're okay with it?
我们半年前就分手了
Look, we've been broken up almost six months.
我是说...我不会为此欢呼
I mean, I'm not thrilled about the idea,
不过他当然有权利跟人约会
but he has every right to date someone else.
非常理智
That's very mature.
你干嘛总拿着电话
Why are you holding the phone?
说的是
Oh, shoot.
真开心  妈妈
That's hilarious, Mom.
她完全没在意
Didn't even notice.
伙计  我喜欢那身衣服
Hey, dude, by the way, I really like that suit.
是什么面料的  进口货吗
Tell me about the fabric. Is it foreign or something?
是进口货  你很识货呀  泰德
Wow. It is foreign. I'm impressed, Ted.
事实上是摩洛哥生产的
- It's Moroccan, actually. - Whoa.
斯华利  电话
I got a call for Swarley.
斯华利在吗
Is there a Swarley here?
你其实对我的衣服 不感兴趣是不是?
You weren't interested in my suit at all, were you?
斯华利?
- Hmm? - Swarley!
是的  我知道他在这里  很重要
Yeah, I know he's there. It's really important.
你能再问一遍吗?
Could you ask again?
斯华利的重要电话
Important call for Swarley!
上帝  你听不见吗  斯华利? 有你的电话
Geez, can't you hear him, Swarley? There's a call for you.
别再那么叫我
Stop calling me that.
让我正式介绍  克洛伊
Uh... Hey, I'd like you guys to officially meet Chloe.
- Hi. - Hi.
Hi.
很高兴认识你们
It's nice to meet you guys.
-我就回来 -在那边
- I'll be right back. - It's right back there.
-怎么样 -怎样?  她很性感
Right? Right? She's hot!
我们很相似
And she likes me?
她喜欢意大利食品  我也喜欢
She likes Italian food. I also like Italian food.
她喜欢比利・乔  我也喜欢...音乐 (流行乐坛巨星)
She likes Billy Joel. I also like... music.
我们还会再约会的
And I think we're going to go out again.
- 你要离她远点儿 - 显而易见
- Dude, you gotta ditch her. - Obviously.
为什么
Why?
她有一双疯眼
She's got the crazy eyes.
老兄  她的眼睛
Dude. The eyes.
它们很不正常
They're crazy.
你们到底在说什么疯眼?
What are you guys talking about, the crazy eyes?
那是对瞳孔状况的书面描述
It's a well-documented condition of the pupils, or pupi.
不  就是瞳孔
No. Just pupils.
它预示着精神状况的不稳定
It's an indicator of future mental instability.
她才没有什么疯眼
She does not have the crazy eyes.
你看不见
You just can't see it because you're afflicted
是因为你已经被激情蒙住了双眼
with "haven't been laid in a while" blindness.
在咖啡店她离得太远
She was too far away in the coffee place,
但刚才近距离观察
but when I saw her up close just now...
让我正式介绍克洛伊
Hey, I'd like you guys to officially meet Chloe.
- Hi. - Hi.
Hi.
很高兴认识你们
It's nice to meet you guys.
告诉你们 我不会因为你们这么说
You  guys, I'm not going to stop dating Chloe
就不再跟她约会
just because you think she has the crazy eyes.
你当然可以继续约她 不过你很快就会后悔的
You can keep going out with her, but you're gonna regret it.
有一次  就在这个酒吧 我碰上一个女孩
One time, I met a girl at this very bar.
我发现她有疯眼...
I saw that she had the crazy eyes...
但我没在意...
...but I ignored it.
毫无疑问
And then, sure enough.
巴尼  能问你个问题?
Barney, can I ask you a question?
当然可以
Anything.
来次3P怎么样?
Would you like to have a threesome?
没问题
Of course.
好极了  就你 我还有鼬鼠先生
Great. It'll be you, me and Mr. Weasels.
你真那么干了?
So, did you do it?
不  最后还是双人游戏
No. It ended up being just a twosome
第三个在椅子上旁观
with the third one watching from a chair.
那你是哪一个
Which one were you?
我看最好别说这个
I'd rather not say.
有一段时间我也不相信疯眼一说
Look, there was a time I didn't believe in the crazy eyes either,
直到我遇到了珍宁
and then I met Jeanine.
她的疯眼非常严重
She had serious crazy eyes.
我告诉自己 那只是我的想象  但...
I told myself I was just imagining it, but then...
我们去喝一杯如何
So, should we go get a drink?
去你的公寓  喝多久都行
As long as it's in your apartment.
哦  对不起
Whoa, I'm sorry.
当心点  看你怎么开车的
Watch! Where! You're! Going!
那么  你住哪儿
So, where do you live?
克洛伊才不会做那种事情
You guys, Chloe is not gonna do any of that stuff.
她是内布拉斯加州的可爱女生
She's a nice girl from Nebraska.
又不是疯子
She's not crazy.
她...她很迷人
She's... she's awesome.
但你不能永远回避 那双疯狂的眼睛
But you can't avoid the crazy eyes forever.
疯狂的本性迟早会浮出水面
Sooner or later, the crazy comes bubbling to the surface.
你好
Hello?
马修  我是克洛伊
Marshall, it's Chloe.
你一连给我打了九次电话?
Are you the one who's called me like nine times?
是  你能来接我吗
Yeah. Could you come get me?
可我正在考试
I'm in the middle of taking a test.
求你了  我很害怕
Please. I'm so scared.
到底怎么了
Well, what's going on?
有个奇怪的侏儒一直跟着我
This weird midget guy started following me
还朝我尖叫
and he was screaming at me
他跛着脚 还是个跎背
and he had a limp and a big hump on his back
警察都不相信我
and the police didn't believe me
我还差点儿伤在马蹄下  还有...
and I almost got trampled by a horse and...
天哪  你一定认为我疯了
God I must sound totally crazy to you right now.
不
No. Pfft.
当然不会
Not at all.
她是极端的疯狂
So, she's needy crazy.
那是最糟糕的状况
That's one of the worst kinds.
我也遇到过那样小妞
I've had one of those.
为了引人注目 编造各种故事
Makes  up stories to get attention.
跟她出门三周 她爸爸可以死两次
Went out with her for three weeks-- her dad died twice.
她是真的吓坏了
Guys, she was really freaked out, okay?
也许故事是真的
Maybe the story is true.
究竟什么能让你 相信那是个真实的故事
What in the world would make you believe that's a true story?
她真的很性感
She's really hot.
她们总是这样
They always are.
- 喝完了吗  泰德? - 是的
- You all done with that, Ted? - Yeah.
内德  我说过叫他内德
Ned. I told you to call him Ned.
真可惜
That's just sad.
对不起  斯华利
Sorry, Swarley.
就你和泰德住在这里
So, do just you and Ted live here
还是斯华利也住这儿
or does Swarley live here, too?
不  斯华利有自己的地方
Nah. Swarley has his own place.
怎么了
What was that?
我刚放下钥匙
Oh, I, uh, dropped my keys.
来了
So, here you go.
两杯南瓜啤酒
Two pumpkin beers.
开个玩笑 只是普通啤酒
I was joking. They're regular beers.
那是什么
What is that?
照框打破了
This picture is broken.
真糟糕
Oh. That's too bad.
那就是莉莉?
Is that Lily?
那个你差点娶过门的女孩?
Is that the girl you were going to marry?
是的 刚才的响声就是这个?
Yeah. Is that what that sound was?
你摔的?
Did you just smash this?
当然不是
No.
我为什么要摔它
Why would I do that?
让我看看你的眼睛
Let me look into your eyes.
没问题
Okay.
我今晚非常开心
I had a really nice time tonight.
我也是  别眨眼
Yeah, me, too. Stop blinking.
我也很喜欢你的眼睛
I  like your eyes a lot, too.
停止
S top!
我是莉莉
Hi. I'm Lily.
停止
Stop!
现在孩子们  我知道 当马修和一个看起很疯狂的女孩约会时
Now, kids, I know Lily hiding in the apartment
莉莉正躲在屋子里
while Marshall was on a date with another girl seems pretty crazy,
但是听听莉莉的故事
but when you hear her side of the story,
那同样也很疯狂
well, it's still pretty crazy.
三天前
斯华利  你怎么样
What's up Swarlz?
别叫了  好吗  别再那么叫了
No. Okay? No. No more.
我不能再让你们那么叫我 就此打住
I will not let this become a thing. It's over.
再没什么斯华利 也没有斯华兹
No more Swarley. No Swarlz.
别再叫斯华利
No more Swar-lay.
听好了  没有什么斯华利
No more Swar... wait for it... ley.
没有  鲍勃・斯华利
No more Bob Swarley, mon.
停止吧  到此为止
No more. No! It's over.
你们的明白?
Do you understand?
知道了
- Yes. - Yes.
多谢
Thank you.
好极了
Nice.
-你为什么不给我打电话 -我该给你打吗
- Why didn't you call me? - Was I supposed to call you?
当然了  告诉我马修 和别的女人约会的事
Yes, about the whole Marshall- dating-another-girl thing.
你说你不介意的
You said you were fine with it.
在泰德面前  我当然要那么说 可我给你使了眼色...
Yeah, in front of Ted, but then I shot you a look.
什么眼色  像这样...
- What look? - This.
那不像是使眼色
That doesn't seem like a look.
那就是  意思是 我很难过  给我打电话
Yes it is. It means, "I'm upset call me later."
你该把我拉到一边 跟我说说那个眼色的含义
You should have pulled me aside and told me what the look meant.
如果能那样 我就不用使眼色了
If I pulled you aside, I wouldn't need the look.
也许那的确是个与众不同的眼神
Well, maybe if it was a more distinctive look...
先别管那个眼色了
Okay, the look isn't important.
重要的是  我受不了
What's important is that I can't stand the idea
马修和别人约会
of Marshall dating another woman.
要是他真爱上别人怎么办?
I mean, what if he falls in love with her?
泰德说那女孩有双疯眼
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
如果这让你好受点儿
Ted says she has the crazy eyes.
什么意思?
What's that?
男人能看出女人的某些特点
Apparently, a thing women have that guys can see
他们认为那女孩儿很疯狂
and it tells them that the girl's crazy.
就好像你从不...
Oh, kind of like how you never want to date a guy
跟指甲修得整齐的男人约会
with perfect fingernails?
古怪的家伙 就是那样
Jerk nails. Exactly.
那么泰德有没有说起 她漂不漂亮?
Well, did-did Ted say whether she was good-looking?
如果我知道她很丑
I mean, 'cause if I knew she was ugly,
可能我就不会那么担心了
then maybe I wouldn't be so freaked out.
他没说  不过你可以自己去看
Uh, he didn't say, but you can find out.
她叫克洛伊  在第78大街 的可萨咖啡店工作
I think her name is Chloe-- she works at Cosa Coffee on 78th.
斯华利・巴克利接电话
Phone call for Swarles Barkley?
你好  泰德  他不在
Hey, Ted. No, he's not here.
很好  那么  记得别忘了
Good one, though-- remember that one.
克洛伊在吗?
Is, um, Chloe here?
她刚走 你也许还能追上她
She just left. You can probably still catch her.
她打着粉红色的伞  很好认的
She's easy to spot-- she's got a pink umbrella.
谢谢你  布莱恩
Oh, thanks, Brian.
我是斯科特
My name is Scott.
你的工号牌写的是布莱恩
Your tag says Brian.
我知道  说来话长...
I know. Funny story.
我早上醒来时...
So, I wake up this morning, and...
好的  再见  布莱恩
Yeah, see you later, Brian.
她就在那儿
There she is.
看起来也不怎么样
She doesn't look that great.
虽然不胖  那也没什么大不了
She's not fat, but that doesn't mean anything.
我可认识不少苗条的丑丫头
I know tons of skinny, ugly women.
就像瑜珈班里的鼻涕虫
That's right, snotty girl in my yoga class,
说的就是你
I'm talking to you.
快点  克洛伊  转过头来
Come on, Chloe, turn around.
快转身  克洛伊
Here we go. Turn around, Chloe.
快点儿  让我看看你那丑样
Come on, show me that hideous face.
该死
Damn it!
对了  我该到她前面
Ooh, I know, I'll get ahead of her,
再转回头这样就能...
then I'll cut back so I... Aah!
天呐  疼死我了
Oh, my God, that hurts!
回头  快点儿
Turn around! Come on!
快回头
Just turn around!
好吧  就疯这一次
Okay, this is ridiculous.
Hey!
快回头  你磨蹭什么
Turn around! What's the matter with you?
嗨  前面的
Hey, you!
回过头来
Turn around!
转身  克洛伊
Turn around, Chloe!
她很漂亮?  真遗憾
She's hot? I'm so sorry.
不  这样也好
No, it's fine.
这样我就能明白
I-It just makes things easier.
她是一个威胁
Now that I know she's a threat,
我得阻止马修再见她
all I have to do is keep Marshall from ever seeing her again.
我有两个计划 你帮我挑一个
Okay, I have two plans-- you can help me choose.
A计划
Plan A--
还记得那次 我和马修的浴室激情?
remember that time Marshall and I had sex in the bathroom?
我简直筋疲力尽
Oops, I got knocked up.
-莉莉 -B计划
- Lily. - Okay, plan B
它叫做克洛伊事件
is called "Chloe's Accident."
- 等一下 - 怎么了
- Just stop. - What?
莉莉  你不能那样做
Lily, you can't do any of those things.
如果你们俩要重归于好
If you two are ever gonna get back together,
你就得让他自己处理这类事情
you have to let him work out whatever this is.
我知道  你说得对
I know. You're right.
走吧  泰德让 我们六点到楼上去
Now, come on, Ted asked us to be upstairs at 6:00.
有个惊喜给巴尼
Some surprise for Barney.
- 巴尼? - 斯华利!
- Barney? - Uh, Swarley.
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
马修呢?
Where's Marshall?
他在理发
Oh, he's getting a haircut.
为他的约会
Oh. For his date.
祝他好运
Good for him.
希望他今晚过得愉快
Hope he has a good time tonight.
放松点 没什么好担心的
Relax, you've got nothing to worry about.
那女孩是疯子
The girl's crazy.
谢谢
Thanks!
他会像野猴子一样 跟她做爱  五次  最多了
He'll just have wild monkey sex with her five times, max,
他会被她榨干的
and be done with her.
多谢了
Thanks again.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
来点音乐  还能怎么样
I just wanted to listen to a little music, that's all.
下一首歌送给斯华利
And this next one's going out to Swarley.
你的朋友们都知道你想念巴尼
All your friends know you miss Barney,
但他已经不在了 你要接受现实  宝贝
but he's gone, and you got to accept that, baby.
这样你才能过得更好  斯华利
And, Swarley, you're gonna be a better woman for it.
这里是海伦・雷迪 主持的 "我是女人" 栏目
Here's "I Am Woman" by Helen Reddy.
现在我是女人了 我喜欢...
Ha-ha! Now I'm a woman. I love it!
我昨天整晚都在想这个新名字
You know, I was thinking about this whole new name thing last night,
知道我发现了什么? 我喜欢这个名字
and you know what I realized? I like it.
你喜欢被叫做斯华利?
You like being called Swarley?
开玩笑  我当然喜欢
Are you kidding? I want you to call me that.
你真这么想?
Do you really think this is gonna work?
那还用问吗 我喜欢我的新名字
Do I think what's gonna work? I'm just saying, I love my new name,
所以  从现在起  就那么叫我
so please only call me that from now on.
叫你什么?
Call you what?
就是那个...那个... 你们常叫的那个...
You know, that-that-that new name that you've been calling me.
说呀
Say it.
干嘛  你们知道那是什么
Why? You guys know what it is.
说出那个名字
Say the name.
不  我不愿意  我恨它
No, I don't want to! I hate it!
我恨它  这不好笑
I hate it! It's not funny!
它根本就没意思 我从没做过任何...
It's never been funny! I've never done any...
不...
No!
当收到那些杂志订阅单时
Man, he is really gonna lose it
他一定会大发雷霆
when all the magazine subscriptions start coming in.
我给他订了《西班牙人》
I signed him up for People in Espanol,
但签的是斯华利
but I addressed it to Swarlos.
马修和我在码头 拍的那张照片在哪?
Hey, where's the picture of Marshall and me at the pier?
它不是总放在窗户旁边?
Didn't it used to be by that window?
你搬走后 他好像把它拿走了
Oh, yeah, he, uh, he sort of took it down when you left.
我想是放到书后面了
Put it behind some books, I think.
也许我该把它放还原
Oh, well-well, maybe I should put it back up.
干嘛?想让克洛伊 看见知难而退?
Why, so Chloe'll see it and get scared off?
不
No.
让马修看着它产生犯罪感
So Marshall'll see it and feel guilty.
算了吧
Yeah, okay.
可她没有就这么算了
But she wasn't okay.
那天晚上 马修还在约会的时候
Later that night, while Marshall was on his date,
莉莉又回来了
Lily came back.
还有吗?
...anymore.
很感人是吗
Pretty impressive, huh?
你真的记住了 我们没有点燃激情  这首诗...
Wow, you really did memorize all the lyrics to "We Didn't Start the Fire."
要喝点什么吗
Can I, uh, can I get you a drink?
啤酒就好
I'd love a beer.
稍等
You got it.
像所有理智的女人一样
Lily did what any sensible woman would do.
莉莉躲到了桌子底下
She hid under the desk.
她待在那里
And she stayed there, listening to her ex-fiance
听着她前未婚夫 和别的女人约会
on a date with another woman.
我今晚非常开心
I had a really nice time tonight.
我也是  别眨眼
Yeah, me, too. Stop blinking.
我也很喜欢你的眼睛
I like your eyes a lot, too.
最后  就像比利・乔
Finally, much like Billy Joel,
她再也受不了
she couldn't take it anymore.
停止
Stop!
我是莉莉
Hi.  I'm Lily.
莉莉... 莉莉 你到底在这里做什么?
Lily... Lily, what the hell are you doing?
我不知道  我也不知道... 在做什么
I don't know. I... I don't know... what I'm doing.
南瓜啤酒  那很好
Oh, pumpkin beer-- that was a good one.
我只是...我走了...很抱歉
I'm just... I'm gonna go. I... I'm so sorry.
你们继续约会
En-Enjoy the rest of your date.
她看起来很不错
She seems nice.
- 莉莉  这是怎么回事? - 对不起...
- Lilly, what the hell... - I'm sorry.
我溜过来是因为...
I only snuck up there because...
昨天我发现她 那么聪明可爱  我很担心
when I saw how cute she was yesterday, I freaked out.
莉莉  你昨天见她了?
Lily, you saw her yesterday?
是的  我跟了她整条街
Yeah, I... kind of chased her down the street.
等等  那你就是 那个驼背跛脚的家伙?
Wait, so you were the hunchback with the limp?
是
Yeah.
她没有打碎像框 是我干的
And she didn't break the picture, I did.
那么克洛伊不是疯子
So Chloe's not crazy, she's...
她只是个可爱的 正常的女孩儿
just a nice, normal girl.
是的
Yeah, she is.
你是该找个 可爱又正常的女孩儿
And you deserve a nice, normal girl.
你干嘛还不上去
So, why don't you just go back up there
继续你的约会
and-and finish your date.
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
好
等等  如果你是那个驼背 她怎么会认为你是男人?
Wait, if you were the hunchback, then why did she think you were a guy?
我是用这种声音叫的
I-I might have used a voice that sounded like this.
- 为什么? - 因为我不想
- Why? - Because I didn't want
让她知道是我 我知道这样很荒唐
her to know it was me, which I now realize doesn't make sense,
她甚至都没见过我
because she hadn't even met me.
你真疯了
You're crazy.
你的眼神比我 见过的任何人都要疯狂
You have... crazier eyes than anybody that I have ever met.
你不是该回去...
Shouldn't you be going back up...
我说  你失去理智了
I mean, you're out of your mind.
你这个大傻瓜
You're... just absolutely insane.
你怎么还不上楼
Shouldn't you be going back upstairs?
我非常想你
I've missed you so much.
我们商量过了
Okay, I ran it by the group,
决定给你个选择机会
and we decided we're gonna give you a choice.
我们同意不再叫你斯华利
We will agree to stop calling you Swarley,
改为叫你詹尼弗
but instead, we'll call you Jennifer.
怎么样
Well?
我在考虑
I'm thinking.
这样如何? 每周一  三  五...
How about this? On Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays...
Hey.
看看这里
Look at this.
就是在这里
So right there, in the exact same place
六个月前在同一个地方 我看到马修孤单一人
that six months earlier I had walked up and found Marshall alone,
为他和莉莉分手而哭泣 现在我又看见他
crying over his breakup with Lily, I found him again.
只是这次他不再孤单
Only this time he wasn't alone,
他很开心
and he was happy.
于是我们去酒吧庆祝 真是棒极了
So we went to the bar to celebrate, and it was great.
我和罗宾在一起 马修和莉莉重归于好
I was with Robin, Marshall and Lily were back together,
巴尼有了一个很酷的新名字
and Barney had a cool new name.
一切都那么美好
All was right with the world...
直到我们回到公寓
until we got back to the apartment.
天呐
Oh, my God.
克洛伊  我...
Hey, Chloe, I...
我好像忘了你还在这里
guess I forgot I left you up here.
我打算走的 可我没找到我的钥匙
I was gonna leave, but I can't find my keys.
它就在咖啡桌上
They're right there on the coffee table.
我真蠢
Silly me.
我把别的地方都找遍了
I must have looked everywhere else.
好了...我要走了
Well... I'm just gonna go.
我们还没见过面 我是克洛伊
Oh, I don't think we've met. I'm Chloe.
罗宾
Robin.
很高兴认识你  罗兰
It's nice to meet you, Roland.
各位再见
I'll see you guys later.
罗兰?
Roland?
你叫罗兰?
Your name's Roland.
很好笑  不是吗
That's funny, right?
罗克和罗兰
Rock and Roland.
华沙是哪里的首都?  罗兰
Warsaw is the capital of what? Roland.
你是莫妮卡・罗兰斯基
You're Monica Roland-ski.
是的  罗兰多好
Hey, yeah, that's just how I Roland.
- 别白费劲  斯华利 - 该死
- Nice try, Swarley. - Damn it.
斯华利
Swarley!
# Sometimes you want to go #
# Where everybody # # knows your name #
# And they're always # # glad you came... #